

Daniel Banciu

Highly motivated student looking for a **Master Thesis**

- Steinenbronner Straße 15, Schönaich, Germany, 71101
- 02.07.1998
- daniel.banciu@student.unituebingen.de
- +49 1573 3191308

SKILLS

Backend Development

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ$

Java, Python, Springboot / VertX, REST

Frontend Development

React|S,

Machine

Learning

PyTorch, Classification, Regression

HTML/CSS

Data Science

 $\bullet \bullet \bullet \circ \circ$ NLP, Clustering

INTERESTS

Karate Jiu-Jitsu

Gaming **Gym**

LANGUAGES

German

Native

Romanian **Native**



Fluent



Italian

English



AWARDS

Deutschlandstipe ndium (scholarship) Deutschlandstipe ndium 2019-2020

I am currently studying MSc Computer Science @University of Tübingen. I am running my own business as an external data protection consultant. Been working both full time and part time as a software developer since 2020. I am very communicative and ambitious.

EDUCATION

(01.10.2021 -University of Tübingen Present) Master of Science. Computer Science

https://uni-tuebingen.de/en/

Heilbronn University of **Applied Sciences**

31.08.2021) 1.7 Bachelor of Science.

Software Engineering

https://www.hs-heilbronn.de/en

Immanuel-Kant-(09.01.2009 -26.07.2017) **Gymnasium** 2.3

General qualification for university entrance

WORK EXPERIENCE

Vector Informatik (16.11.2020 -28.03.2023) **GmbH**

Software Developer

Bachelor Thesis, Full-Time in between Bachelor and Master, working student

https://www.vector.com

(01.04.2018 -Created own small Present) husiness

External data protection consultant

External data protection consultant and IT consultant specialized for dentists

eXXcellent solutions consulting & software **GmbH**

(14.02.2020 -31.10.2020)

(01.09.2017 -

Software Developer

Internship and then working student

https://exxcellent.de/

BACHELOR THESIS

Predictive Analysis of Electric (01.01.2 021 -Vehicles during Charging to 30.06.2 **Optimize Load Management** 021)**Algorithms**

Bachelor Thesis at Vector GmbH

Implementation of a new feature that collects information about electric vehicles and their charging behaviour for an existing load management product.

Energy, Load Management, Java, Electric Vehicles

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Digitale Sprechstunde

IT consulting "hour"

Helping old people with all IT-related things such as setting up their first smartphone and explaining how to write e-mails etc.

Jugendgemeinderat (local politics youth council)

founding member 2016

https://www.leinfelden-

echterdingen.de/Startseite/Stadt/Ju gendgemeinderat.html

PROJECTS

BUGA 2019 App

Bachelor "big project" at Heilbronn
Development of an application for the
Bundesgartenschau 2019 in Heilbronn
as part of the big project in the 5th
semester of the bachelor's degree.
Fullstack-Developer and Scrum Master.
Fullstack, Java, React, Scrum

Self Driving Cars Machine Learning Challenges

Self Driving Cars course at Tübingen Challenges involved imitation learning and reinforcement learning using the car gym environment.

Machine Learning, PyTorch

Fair Machine Learning Seminar

Fair Machine Learning Seminar at Tübingen

Evaluation the effectiveness of attribution methods for tabular data. Comparing the performance of SHAP and LIME attribution methods. Using a transformer-based language model, known as GReaT.

https://github.com/dbanciutue/tab ular-ROAD

Explainable Machine Learning, Attribution Methods

NLP Analysis

Course Project of "Data Literacy" at Tübingen

Analysis of an unknown data set in a project in teams of two. We analysed every speech in the Bundestag and tried to answer questions like "How has the language developed?"

Data Science, NLP

Pose Estimation Machine Learning

Praktikum Bildverarbeitung, Maschinelles Lernen und Computer Vision

As part of the course "Praktikum Bildverarbeitung, Maschinelles Lernen und Computer Vision" we show how we developed a pytorch implementation of the paper 'Toward fast and accurate human pose estimation via soft-gated skip connections'.

https://github.com/Human-Pose-Estimation-Tubingen/Stacked_Hourglass_paper

Machine Learning, PyTorch

Daniel Banciu

Rund Dan